Same, just how do you evaluate how today
went for you?
I think
God has been good to me. Um
I'm lucky to be out here, you know, uh
after the injuries and everything and
just self-reflection, you know, it's I'm
just grateful that I had an opportunity
to come out here and and work with my
guys, you know, I was excited to see
those guys. I think it was just a great
day to get some work. I think got a lot
to clean up on, but hey, you know, like
I said, you know, if you if you're
getting better, you're not getting
better, you're getting worse, so I think
I got better today, so
I'm like I said, I'm glad to be here.
So, what worked for you today? What do
you think worked for you to say, "Hey,
this really impressed the scouts." What
did you feel? Um I think I did pretty
well in changing direction. Uh I think
my 40 looked smooth, um I would say, but
uh I think definitely change direction
for sure.
You would make kind of a late decision
to participate in this at pro day here.
What kind of went into all that in
deciding to compete?
So, like I said, my Lord and Savior, um
I had a lot of time just away from ball,
away from everything, you know, um just
having a lot of time to
you know, deepen my faith and uh
just letting God use me and speak to me
and uh
it led me back here, so I must be here
for a reason, so like I said, ready to
get back to work.
You played through the injury, you
obviously weren't 100%. What did you How
close to 100% are you now given that
>> [laughter]
>> Did that play a a role in whether you
were deciding whether to do this? Yeah,
that definitely played a huge role into
why I decided that I would be done. Um
the injuries and whatnot, you know, I
just felt like my body was just
just worn out, you know, and I just
feel like I needed that recovery, that
break, and I think over time, like I
think I'm I'm refreshed, you know, I
feel a lot better now, so like I said,
I'm just
I'm excited, man. I'm glad to be back.
Feels good.
>> though? Like the NFL teams, they say you
played through the injury, like what
does that just say about you? How much
does that help your stock in terms of
trying to get to the NFL?
Hey, man.
Like I told them before, like all I know
is everything Every time you step on the
field, you got to earn it, so um just
having that mindset regardless of to
what the narratives are about me, you
know, I just want to come out here and
just work, you know, give it all I got
every snap, and now I'm glad I'm able to
do that, you know, having that rest now.
I get to come out here and give it
everything I got now, which is what it's
all about, so yeah.
What's the feedback been like for you?
Been good. Um I think everyone was just
skeptical about like whether or not, you
know, I was going to play or not, so now
everyone knows. I think everything
[snorts] is better now, and obviously
came out here to do the workout, so I
think I will hear some more feedback
here soon.